Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and forge ahead, drawing your own map as you go!
We can't even tell left from right
in this tempest-tossed era
Even the values we've honed
seem ready to crumble
Is the compass leading us true,
or is it leading us astray?
Nobody knows for sure!
Just breathe deep, close your eyes
and you'll find your soul guiding the way!
Reach your hands out,
cut through the wind,
and kick away the darkness!
I'm doing this for myself,
and you're doing this for yourself too, right?
Forge ahead, painting the world in your own colors!
The Thunder Bagua...
I thought I defended against it...
Yet, it was
nowhere near enough...
Yamabro!
Go help "Gutless" out!
Wh-Who are you calling "Gutless"?!
Go do the damn thing
already, Momo!
S-Silence!
I am fully aware of what I must do!
Do you truly believe people
can change so easily?!
Fear not, Momonosuke-kun!
I am coming with you!
Apologies for leaving you earlier!
Yamato!
Well, then!
Let us stop Onigashima!
Countin' on ya, Momo!
Hey, Yamato!
Momonosuke!
Where the hell do you
think you're going?!
Lend me your strength...
Kin'emon!
Kiku!
I will surely...!
Make haste, Momonosuke-kun!
Yamabro!
I understand!
You want to face him
in a duel, aye?
Yup!
I am going to diiiie!
Mo...
Momonosuke-kun!
Clutch the sky!
Clutch?!
Dragons can create clouds!
C-Create?!
You are a dragon now!
You can do it!
I am... a dragon.
I create...
...clouds!
I know...
I know how!
That's it!
Kin'emon!
Take Momonosuke-sama and flee!
I will...
...Surely come back to you,
my retainers!
Dragons do not merely fly!
They create clouds, clutch them,
and dash through the skies!
Such are dragons!
I am flyilling!
These clouds are called...
...Flame Clouds!
Momonosuke-kun!
Look!
This is most unusual!
The island is starting to collapse!
What?!
Is that a... problem?
It cannot be...
Kaido is...
...losing strength!
The Flame Clouds Kaido created
are becoming unstable,
and they can no longer support
the fracturing bedrock!
We must hurry then!
I care not what hapens to me!
I shall not permit such a treacherous thing
to make its way to the Flower Capital!
You mustn't,
Momonosuke-kun!
I grew so that I could
stop this island!
You cannot,
Momonosuke-kun!
This is not the way!
But we do not have time!
And lo!
We are very nearly at the capital!
It will arrive
in less than five minutes!
Out with the
Flame Clouds, then!
With those colossal,
draconic clouds,
Kaido is moving Onigashima!
To push it back, you must create
more powerful Flame Clouds than his!
That is impossible!
cannot possibly produce such things!
I have barely learned flight!
Besides, I do not necessarily share
the same powers as he!
But you can conjure Flame Clouds!
I am sure you are capable!
It is all in our hands now.
The situation is more dire
than we thought!
Even if it lands as Kaido plans,
there will be numerous
casualties in the capital!
In the worst-case scenario...
Should Kaido runs out of strength,
the Flame Clouds will disappear,
sending Onigashima hurtling to the ground!
Stored within Onigashima are
unfathomable quantities of weapons...
...and gunpowder!
Onigashima is practically
a titanic bomb!
And it is much too close...
There is not enough time for
the citizenry to evacuate!
Should the island come down,
enemy and ally alike
will meet a grisly fate!
Eh?!
Then we must stop Luffy!
Fool!
He already totters on the precipice,
bearing the world upon his shoulders!
'Tis only he who can fell Kaido!
We mustn't burden him further
with this development!
We shall weather this storm,
and with none the wiser!
Hit the deck!
King-sama's totally flipped!
Zoro!
What happened to you?!
King the Wildfire...
He ain't an All-Star for nothin'.
He's damn strong...
No surprise there.
The hell's goin' on,
over on the Floor?
Need a hand?
Nah, I'm good!
Dammit, King!
Don't just throw out random attacks!
You cut my butt!
Better if it were your neck!
Pirate Hunter Zoro...
damaged King-san's mask!
Yeah, that would piss him off...
Nobody knows what he looks like
under that mask!
Sorry, Franky...
Better steer clear!
Gotcha, hang in there!
Three-Sword Style:
Imperial...
...Archer!
Ultra Tiger...
...Hunt!
What the?!
Wait...
I'm gonna fall!
Two-Sword Style:
Clear Lance!
Close one...!
At least use your
damn sword to kill me!
I ain't lettin' you off!
Same to you!
Do you doubt me?
Think I'm lying, perhaps?
Never said that.
What I'm saying is, another dragon that isn't Kaido
made their appearance.
This must be the Devil Fruit-
Vegapunk created!
And they appear to be
allied with Straw Hat Luffy.
That's fine, isn't it?
Just pirates trying to put each other out of business.
Then, what did you call us for?
Got orders from above.
"If by any chance Kaido loses...
"the Land of Wano,
a non-member state of the World Government,
"is to be brought under
direct control of the Government."
We've already
dispatched ships to Wano...
Seizing a country by force, huh?
No better than
pirates themselves...
What are the odds
that Kaido loses?
In the beginning, Kaido had 30,000 troops,
but that shrank to 12,000...
It is a fascinating battle,
I'll admit...
I can't see
Kaido actually falling, however.
I didn't think so...
Keep me updated.
# Oh, and...
One more order that came down:
Bring Nico Robin in!
Further failure
will not be tolerated.
We know.
Clik.
You expect I would hand over
a friend of mine?!
Three-Verse Humming:
Nock Slash!
How was I?
Was I the slightest bit helpful?
Yes, quite!
Whoa!
Are you all right?
Thank you, Brook.
There she is!
It's Nico Robin!
Don't let her get away!
Nab her!
My, my!
They've sent the horde!
You're quite
the popular one, Robin-san!
It's a bother, really!
Whatever shall I do?
I know how hard it is,
being the center of attention.
But don't you worry
shall defend you, come what may!
Most reassuring, Brook!
Careful,
or I'll get carried away!
Stop right there!
Come forth!
O stronger clouds!
Tis progressing
faster than I thought...
The speed of its collapse...!
Listen, Momonosuke-kun!
I shall return to the Skull Dome,
to minimize the damage that may come
from the worst possible outcome.
Whaaaa?!
There are countless explosives
in the giant armory beneath the dome...
...that I must somehow
dispose of,
lest the worst comes to pass,
and the damage caused is
multiplied many times over!
I shall leave this task to you!
Eh?!
You would leave me behind?!
I am certain you can summon
Flame Clouds more powerful than Kaido's!
Damn! Damn!
Damn it all!
I summon thee, Flame Clouds!
How could he...
...leave me alone?!
Nay!
No more petty grousing, Momonosuke!
You can do this!
I know you can!
Alas, I cannot!
Nay, nay
I must do this!
Create clouds, then clutch them!
I summon thee...
Flame Clouds!
I summon thee!
I must do this,
else many of my people will perish!
I will not let this island...
...this massive bomb, fall!
What?!
A huge wolf?!
It is in your hands now,
Momonosuke-kun!
I summon thee, Flame Clouds!
Because it is you...
...you will succeed!
Vinsmoke Sanji!
Dance with me some more!
Flying Pan!
I'm a super machine gun!
Ain't nobody gonna
stop my funk!
Heavy!
My attacks won't stop comin'!
C'mon, show it to me...
Germa 66's combat suit!
Sanji!
You were showinoff your combat suit
to King, weren't ya?!
I'm pretty damn sure
you went invisible right then!
That's Judge's
scientific smarts for ya!
Stupid ass loudmouth lizard!
Man, I really am feeling off...
Put on that suit, Vinsmoke!
I told you to
drop that damn name!
You don't know squat about
what's going on in my family!
Scratch that,
they're not my family at all!
I ain't wearing that crap!
Black...
...Light Roast!
Diable Jambe:
Bien Cuit...
...Gril Shot!
No damage?!
But that was Sanji-san's kick!
What'm I gonna do...
...about this dino's toughness?
Pretty good kick,
for plain ol' flesh 'n blood.
Well, how bout I show you
what an unmodified dino can really do...!
Show you the power of those that dominated the world
for over a hundred million years!
Puny humans...
On your knees!
Here it comes!
The true power of the ancients!
Cry! Scream!
Cower in fear!
Here I go!
Brachiosnakeus!
Hwuuuuh?!
Hwuw-
That's how it works!!
Ah, crap!
You dropped your guard!
This's the kind of dino
a brachiosaurus is!
You don't say...
Dammit!
Now you see the true power of the dinosaur,
king of the ancient world!
Nobody's ever gotten loose
from the Brachiocoilus!
LN
Sangoro-san!
Sanji-san's done for
if this keeps up!
He's in real danger!
A human body can't stand that!
Sanji!
Who knew dinosaurs
were this terrifying...!
Sangoro san!
Not even a master of
Conqueror's Haki...
...can prevent my pressure from
shattering their bones and crushing their organs!
Anyone caught in it
ain't comin' back!
Done so soon,
son of Judge?!
If you show me what
Germa's got cookin',
I'll let ya go.
I refuse...!
Check that out!
Were I just any old brachiosaurus...
my torso and legs
would be totally useless!
But... I'm a scientist!
Torso-mounted super weapons!
A genius idea
for making use of the useless!
All I gotta do is call out their name,
and they'll come flyinright at ya!
They're the
Brachio Launchers!
Queen-sama!
No!
was just...
...explaining...
You damned piece o' junk!
Do it only when I shout it out like an attack...!
Like this: Brachio Launchers...
Queen-sama!
M-Man...
I pack a helluva punch...
But! My constriction technique's decided things!
This fight's over!
You are already... dead.
Every bone in his body's
got to be broken,
and there's no way
his internal organs're intact...
We must administer
the super-restorative!
Yes!
Whaaaa?!
Are you all right, my boy?!
Well, it definitely hurts,
but I can move around like I usually do...
You're scarin' me, Sanji...
Did you turn into a zombie?!
A zombie?
What's...
What's happening to my body?!
Don't tell me...
...I've awakened the same
enhancements as them....
Sanji!
Stay focused!
Behind you!
I'm back to myself?
Ya little runt!
Ouch.
What?
I don't wanna...
...become a monster...
...like any of them!